Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 7=
Watch your back.
You should know,
many people are eyeing
your position as City Lord.
Don't end up like your father.
Thank you for your guidance.
Let me walk you out.
This way.
Is everything fine?
I tried to bring you
the City Lord Token last night.
But I was caught.
The City Lord Token isn't here.
Why didn't Lord Duan give you trouble?
Things may have changed
in the imperial court again.
His Majesty is deeply concerned,
fearing that some City Lords
might commit treason.
Safe and sound.
Keeping the City Lord Token safe
is our only chance to maneuver.
Wan.
Being my wife
might not be as ideal as you imagine.
It could put you in grave danger.
I know that perfectly well.
How do you know?
I didn't just come
to bring you the City Lord Token.
I need to talk to you.
(Divorce Agreement)
Mu Yunqing, let's get divorced.
Get divorced?
Sign it and you'll be free.
Are you really marrying Song Qiming?
Mr. Song is sweet and considerate.
He cares only for me.
His look and status
are no worse than yours.
He makes a great husband.
You said you'd come to me.
I believed you.
Now, you're marrying him instead.
Yu Yingwan, I really don't get it.
Childhood sweethearts
were just putting up a show.
You told me that back then.
Now, take it as my reply.
Don't you remember what you did
on our wedding day?
And you expect me to love you?
♪Perish before the flowers♪
Don't make this hard. Just sign it.
I'll ask you one last time.
Do you really love Song Qiming?
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
Yes, I do.
♪You're the untouchable star♪
For the sake
of our old days,
just sign it.
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
If that's what you want,
I'll grant your wish.
Farewell.
♪Spend all my devotion♪
(Yunqing, I have to do this)
(to stay in Shili Pavilion
and find the culprit.)
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You remain so distant♪
♪Yet stand before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
Get divorced.
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
It's for the best.
She'll be safe like this.
And I can rest easy.
This City Lord's Mansion
will be left in peace.
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪
♪Falling into dream's abyss♪
♪Some kind of call♪
♪My beloved one♪
♪Severing past bonds♪
Wei Feng.
♪Pain clings too stubbornly♪
Wei Feng, bring me wine!
Hurry.
My lord.
Why are you drinking so much?
Come on, drink with me.
My lord, you should stop drinking.
Even if you drown yourself in wine,
it won't change
the fact that you're divorced.
Mr. Song is kind and handsome.
And he spends on me.
Unlike you who only makes me mad.
Forgot how you refused to leave
the City Lord's Mansion?
In that case,
let's get divorced.
Be careful.
Get divorced?
I haven't signed it.
So this divorce agreement is invalid.
My lord,
Madam has returned to Shili Pavilion.
She asked me to tell you
that it doesn't matter if you sign.
She won't come back.
It doesn't matter?
(Shili Pavilion)
Yu Yingwan, come out.
Yu Yingwan.
Come out.
Wan.
I don't want to divorce you anymore.
Come out.
Won't you even see me?
Yu Yingwan.
Won't you even see me one last time?
My lord, let's go home.
Madam won't come out.
This way. Be careful.
Wei Feng, go.
Buy me another jar of wine.
I want more.
Get the exact wine Wan loved most.
Go on.
If you won't go, I'll go myself.
My lord.
Hang them over there.
♪This endless yearning♪
My lord, please leave.
Miss Yu is about to
marry our young master.
Please go home.
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
(I'm really going to lose you.)
(Wan.)
(May your life be filled
with endless blessings.)
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪